Hey ji, as soon as you go to the market, first feed me Pani
Puri, if I do
n't feed you then start by eating Pani Puri once and make up for the
expenses,
today I will just eat for ₹20,
yes, okay, come on,
sit,
but in a second
I will kill you, come on,
say it again,
wow, what a scene.
What a weather it is.
Oh Lord, Oh Lord, I will have to
play your game.
Hey Baba, I am
finished, I am down.
Hey, what are you doing in the drain, go quickly wash your face and ears and go to the
market
[Music]
Come on, come on, come on,
brother, feed him Pani Puri too,
yes
[Music]
I should meet you like this, oh my god, I have
spoiled your mood, thief thief thief,
oh brother, oh my god, you are gone
son
[Music]
Brother
Kalwa,
Jai Mahishmate, wait, be
patient
[Laughter]
You bastard, thief, give me your purse, give me your purse, get out,
wow, what an acting you are doing,
now you have been caught after getting clean,
brother, take this ₹20, hey, not ₹20, give me
₹000, I
ate ₹000 worth of things, look at that at home,
but wait a second,
injustice has been done to me.  I have been wronged.